Hello I am here.
Hi.
Hi! I'm Samantha.
Imagine a
banking app
In which
you said
transfer ₹50
to Amit
As per your
instructions, I have
transferred ₹50
to Amit and
he will do it.
Nowadays our
interaction with
Computer is becoming
more like
we're talking
to human .
Basically to chatter.
Let's look at
a little history
of UX UI.
Come, first of
all punchcard type
computers came
around 1970's,
In which you
have to insert
the punchcard and
it will execute
the program.
Then came
computer systems
with command line
interface, In which
you give commands
in scripting language
to computer in
order to interact
with them.
After that
came graphical
user interface GUI,
In which mouse
was invented to
interact with them.
Because the mouse
works like
pointer.
Then came touch
screen mobiles
phone ,which does
not require mouse
and keyboard
external hardware.
The work
is done only
with touch screen.
Now today
chaat pods are
used everywhere ,
like Chatgpt
These computer
systems have
become as if
you are now
talking to
another human being.
It's fun now,
isn't it?
So humanity is
now moving forward
like this.
Think how you
can make a
product in
this direction